marketingmerge.com 2016-11-01

# Policies

* * *

###  Thank you for visiting the Coaching Cognition website.

We take your privacy seriously and are committed to protecting your privacy online. Please read this policy to understand how your personal information will be treated as you take advantage of the information and services available at our website. 

###  Overview

This Privacy Policy governs your use of this Coaching Cognition, LLC website. It describes what information we collect from you; what cookies are used and how they are used; how your information is utilized; who is collecting your information; with whom your information may be shared; the types of security precautions in place to protect against loss, misuse, or alteration of your information; how we protect children's privacy; and other details you may want to know about your privacy at our website. 

Please note that our privacy practices are subject to change from time to time. Please visit this page periodically to ensure you follow the most current version of this Privacy Policy. All amended terms will be effective after being posted on our website. 

By visiting our website, you agree to be bound by the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree with the terms of this Privacy Policy, please do not use or access our website. 

###  What Personally Identifiable Information do we collect?

The primary purpose of collecting information from you is to provide you with a safe, smooth, effective, and personalized experience and to fulfill the transactions you undertake here. We only collect information about you that we consider necessary to achieve this purpose.

Generally, we collect information in three ways. Some information is gathered when you access secure areas within our website. This may include your name, email address, street address, and phone number. Where possible, we indicate which fields are required and which fields are optional. We may also collect personal information when you contact us with questions or feedback. If you contact us, we may keep a record of that correspondence or conversation to better serve you going forward. 

Finally, you also will have to provide us with credit card and other payment information necessary to complete a payment from you. We use a third party to process and verify credit cards for billing purposes. This requires us to share your name, credit card number, expiration date and billing address with the credit card processing company. When processing a payment transaction we will also obtain information regarding the amount of the payment and other transaction data. We may transfer or disclose this payment information to a third party only to the extent necessary in order to complete the payment processing. 

###  What are "cookies" and how do we use them?

Data collection devices, such as "cookies," are used to store, and sometimes track, information about you. Generally, these cookies help provide personalized services and promote trust and safety. A cookie is a small file containing a small amount of data that is sent to your browser from a web server and placed on your computer's hard drive to assist us in providing our services. All pages on the website where you are prompted to login or that are customizable request that you accept cookies. Cookies are only read by the server that placed them and are unable to execute any code or virus. Most cookies are "session cookies," and are automatically deleted from your hard drive at the end of a session. No personally identifiable information is collected with the cookies that we place. 

More specifically, we use cookies to remind us of who you are and to access your account information in order to deliver to you a more personalized service. We also use cookies, along with IP addresses, to measure your visiting patterns in the aggregate. We use this research to understand how our users' habits are similar or different from one another so that we can make each new experience on our website a better one. We may also use this information to better personalize the content, banners, and promotions that you and other users will see on our website. 

###  How do we use your information?

We use your information to provide you with a customized website experience. We also may use your personal information to manage and monitor your purchases or training with us; communicate with you; resolve disputes; troubleshoot problems; manage and operate our marketing programs; detect and protect against error, fraud, or other criminal activity; and enforce our Terms and Conditions of Use Agreement. 

From time to time, we may use your personal information to send important notices, such as communications about our services and changes to our terms, conditions, and policies. Because this information is important to your interaction with us, you may not opt out of receiving these communications.

###  Who is collecting information?

When you are using our website and are asked for personal information, you are sharing that information with Coaching Cognition, LLC and, if you arrived at the website via an affiliate link or affiliate of Coaching Cognition, LLC, then with that affiliate as well. 

Please be advised that the Coaching Cognition, LLC affiliates, advertisers, and websites that have links on our websites may collect personally identifiable information about you. The information practices of those affiliates, advertisers, and websites are not covered by this Privacy Policy. 

###  Who do we share your information with?

We will not disclose, sell or rent your personally identifiable information unless we have your permission or under certain limited circumstances, such as those described below. 

_Affiliates:_ If you have visited our website through a link provided by an affiliate of Coaching Cognition, LLC , we will share your personally identifiable information with that affiliate responsible for your visit and that affiliate may contact you. 

_Employees, Associates, Instructors, Coaches and Consultants:_ To help deliver our services and information, we may provide your personally identifiable information to our employees, associates, instructors, coaches and consultants. All of our employees, associates,instructors, coaches and consultants are subject to non-disclosure agreements with us. Which prohibit their use of the information you provide us for any purpose except to facilitate the operation and activities of Coaching Cognition, LLC, unless you agreed or gave your prior permission to them for additional uses. 

_Third Party Data & Data in the Aggregate:_ Aggregate data (data gathered across all user accounts) may be gathered in a non-personally identifiable form to build higher quality, more useful online services by performing statistical analyses of the collective characteristics and behavior of our visitors, and by measuring demographics and interests regarding specific areas and services of our website. Aggregate data may be disclosed in a non-personally identifiable manner to advertisers and other third parties for their marketing and promotional purposes. However, no personal information that could be used to identify you personally is disclosed in these situations. 

_External Service Providers:_ Separate services are offered by third parties, also known as external service providers, some of whom advertise on our website or are linked to us from our website. If you choose to disclose information to these parties or grant them permission to collect information about you, then their privacy policies will govern that use of your information. We will not disclose your personal information to external service providers without your express consent. 

_Business Transaction:_ Coaching Cognition, LLC reserves the right to transfer any and all information that we collect from visitors, or that we otherwise collect concerning or in connection with our website, to a third party in the event that Coaching Cognition, LLC enters into a business transaction such as a reorganization, merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, in which case your personally identifiable information may be among the assets transferred. 

_Other:_ We may disclose account information when we have reason to believe that disclosing the information is necessary to identify, contact, or bring legal action against someone who either intentionally or unintentionally may be violating our Terms and Conditions of Use Agreement or may be causing injury to or interference with our rights or property, other users of our website, or anyone else that could be harmed by such activities. We may disclose or access account information when we believe in good faith that the law requires it and for administrative and other purposes that we deem necessary to maintain and improve our services. 

We cannot ensure that all of your private communications and other personal information will never be disclosed in ways not otherwise described in this Privacy Policy. For example, we may be forced to disclose information to the government or third parties. Under certain circumstances, third parties may unlawfully intercept or access transmissions or private communications, or other users may abuse or misuse your personal information that they collect from our website. Although we use industry standard practices to protect your privacy, we do not promise, and you should not expect, that your personal information or private communications will always remain private. 

###  What security precautions are in place to protect the loss, misuse, or alteration of my information?

We’ll make every reasonable effort, both through how we perform our services and available technology solutions, to protect your private data. Whenever we handle your personal information, we take steps to ensure that your information is treated securely and in accordance with the relevant Terms and Conditions of Use Agreement and this Privacy Policy. We use procedural and mechanical safeguards to protect your personal information against loss or theft as well as unauthorized access and disclosure to protect your privacy, including encryption. Unfortunately, however, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. We cannot, therefore, warrant or ensure the security of any information you transmit to us or from our online products or services, and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission, we make our best effort to ensure its security on our systems. 

###  How are children's privacy protected?

Children under the age of 18 are not authorized to use our website and we ask that children do not submit any personal information to us. 

###  You are responsible for protecting your access information

We recommend that you change your password periodically. Your password should be at least 6 characters in length and contain a combination of letters, numbers and special characters. You are responsible for maintaining the security of your user name and password. If you believe that they have been stolen or otherwise made known to others, you should contact us immediately at support@coachingcognition.com and change them immediately. We are not responsible if someone else accesses your account through access information they have obtained from you, as a result of your negligence or through a violation by you of this Privacy Policy or our Terms and Conditions of Use Agreement. 

If you have a security-related concern, please contact us at support@coachingcognition.com. We will work closely with you to ensure a rapid and personal response to your concerns. 

###  Additional Information

Any questions regarding this statement should be directed to: [ support@coachingcognition.com](mailto:support@coachingcognition.com)
